cloudbees.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy | CloudBees

_Last updated: July 1,  2014_

This Privacy Policy describes how CloudBees, Inc. (“CloudBees” “We,” “Us,” or “Our”) protects your privacy when you use the Web site located at www.cloudbees.com (the “Site”).

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS DESCRIBED HEREIN AND ALL TERMS AND CONDITIONS INCORPORATED BY REFERENCE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH BELOW, YOU MAY NOT USE THE  SITE.**

This Privacy Policy applies to information (including, personal information) collected through the Site. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, “personal information” means information that identifies you personally, either alone or in combination with other information available to us. Personal information does not include “aggregate” information, which is data we collect about the use of the Site, or about a group or category of products, services or users, from which individual identities or other personal information has been removed. This policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate information, and we may share aggregate data about our users with third parties for various purposes. This Privacy Policy is part of and incorporated into CloudBees’s Terms of Service, http://www.cloudbees.com/terms-service (“Terms of Service”).

**CLOUDBEES’S PRIVACY PLEDGE TO  YOU**

  * We are committed to protecting your privacy while allowing you to use the Site.
  * You may add, delete or modify your personal information at any time.
  * Subject to your permission or as specifically stated in this Privacy Policy, we will not sell, exchange or otherwise share your personal information with third parties.
  * We do not send spam, maintain spam mailing lists or support the activities of spammers.

* * *

**WHAT** **PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT ON THE SITE AND HOW WE COLLECT  IT**

Active Collection of Information

Personal information may be collected in a number of ways when you visit the Site, purchase products or use any of the services offered via the Site. We may collect certain information that you voluntarily provide to us which may contain personal information. For example, we may collect your name, email address, user name, telephone number and payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address) when you register, set up an account, contact us by e-mail or purchase services from the Site. Regarding credit card information, CloudBees uses a third-party intermediary to manage credit card processing and this intermediary is not permitted to store, retain, or use this information except to process your credit card information for CloudBees. For more details on how this third party stores credit card information, please contact us at info@cloudbees.com.

Passive Collection of Information

When you visit the Site, some information may be automatically collected. For example, it is standard for your Web browser to automatically send information to every Web site you visit including ours. Such information includes your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, access times, browser type and language, and referring Web site addresses. We may also collect information about your computer’s operating system and information about your usage and activity on the Site.

Cookies

We may automatically collect certain information through the use of “cookies.” Cookies are small data files that are stored on your hard drive by a Web site. Among other things, the use of cookies helps us to improve the Site and your experience on the Site. We use cookies to see which areas and features of the Site are most popular, to count the number of computers accessing the Site, to personalize your experience and to remember your preferences. If your browser is set not to accept cookies or if you reject a cookie, you may not be able to access certain features or services of the Site.

Web Beacons

Web beacons, also known as gifs, are electronic images that may be used on the Site or in our emails. A Web beacon may be used on our Web pages to collect information, deliver cookies, count visits, compile statistics on usage and campaign effectiveness and in our emails to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

**STORAGE OF INFORMATION & TRANSFER OF DATA ABROAD**

Most of the information we collect is retained by us on our servers. If you are visiting the Site from a country other than the country in which our Web servers are located (currently the United States of America) the various communications will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting the Site and communicating electronically with us, you consent to the processing and transfer of your data as set out in this Privacy Policy.

**HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL  INFORMATION**

We use the information collected through the Site: (i) to communicate with you; (ii) to process your requests and transactions; (iii) to improve the Site; (iv) to customize the services and/or products we provide to you; (v) to assist with our product and service development; (vi) to perform marketing analysis; and (v) for other purposes related to our business.

**WITH WHOM WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL  INFORMATION**

Personal information collected through the Site may be shared with companies and organizations that perform services on our behalf; for example, companies that provide data management or other support services to us, such as data storage and Web hosting services.

Also, we may disclose the personal information we collect through the Site when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to: (i) comply with applicable law (or a court order or subpoena); (ii) prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; (iii) enforce the Terms of Service or other agreements that govern your use of the Site and/or our services; (iv) to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users or others; or (v) to protect your vital interests.

Personal information submitted to the Site or collected by us is our asset and will become part of our normal business records. Your personal information and other data collected by us may be transferred to another company that has acquired our stock or assets, for example, as a result of a sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or liquidation. If such a transfer occurs, the acquiring company’s use of your personal information will still be subject to this Privacy Policy, and the privacy preferences you have expressed to us.

**MODIFYING YOUR INFORMATION; OPT-OUT TO PROMOTIONAL  MATERIALS**

We respect your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use and disclose your personal information. You may update or modify your information or change your privacy preferences at any time by emailing us at info@cloudbees.com or, in some instances, via the Site.

You may “opt-out” of receiving promotional communications including, without limitation, promotional emails, from us by emailing us at info@cloudbees.com or by clicking on the unsubscribe link on the bottom of non-operational communications we may send to you. Transactional service communications including, but not limited to, messages about your registration, will not be subject to the foregoing opt-in procedures.

**Click _here_ to review our Canada Anti-Spam Legislation (CASL) Compliance Policy for information concerning our compliance with the requirements of CASL.**

**SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL  INFORMATION**

We take reasonable security measures to protect your personal information (including, preventing the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction of your personal information). Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are impenetrable.

If you use a password on the Site, you are responsible for keeping it confidential. Do not share it with any other person. If you believe your password has been misused, please advise us immediately.

**MINORS**

THIS SITE IS NOT MEANT FOR MINORS. We are committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. The Site is not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and we do not target the Site to children under 13.

We may not intend to collect or solicit information from people who are minors. However, as a condition of use for minors in those countries or regions where information gathering from minors is considered illegal, guardians will be responsible for accompanying minors for prevention of any unexpected circumstances when they access the Site.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY  POLICY**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time-to-time. If we make any changes to this Privacy Policy, we will change the “Last Updated” date above. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you visit the Site to understand how your personal information is used.

**QUESTIONS**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by emailing [info@cloudbees.com](mailto:info@cloudbees.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).
